Anna Rusyayeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

SUMMARY

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

SKILLS

- **Agile** (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- Managing projects (Trello, Jira)
- E-commerce (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- **Marketing** (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, moqups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer December 2018

- Mobile app development
- Websites development
- Payment system development

Front end developer – Bank Tochka

Local CRM system modules development

- Bank app modules developments
- Mobile app modules development
- Local ht portal modules development

Senior Marketing Manager - 000 'Ideco'

October 2017 - June 2018

July 2018 – July 2019

- Project management (launch, maintaining and updating)
- Development process management (technical specifications for designers and developers)
- Organisation Agile workflow (Jira, Trello)
- Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- SMM
- POSM
- Sales analytics
- · Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities



PROJECTS

Landing Page



Development + marketing strategy

Landing Page



Development + marketing strategy

Catalog of projects



Web catalog development based on printed one

Domain relocation



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses

SEO Specialist - Advertising Agency 'Index Art'

January 2017 – October 2017

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Task management Technical auditing (developers, designers, writers)
- Creation and testing of hypotheses for increasing traffic (ui/ux, structure, HTML, core, content)
- Attendance and behavior analytics
- Creating monthly reports for customers

НОЧЛЕЖКА

Website

Design + development.



Newsletter for the company.

Emailing



Mobile App



App for iOS & Android

Payment system

Context Advertising and SEO Specialist -

December 2015 - September 2016

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex. Direct, Google AdWords, MyTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

Software Engineer -

October 2013 - September 2014

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

- Writing technical specification for software
- Detecting of software functionality flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing

EDUCATION

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics Master of Computer Science

February 2015

App for shools

Ural Federal University

2015

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration

Ural Federal University

2013

LANGUAGES

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

Ural Federal University

2013

Russian native speaker English - B2

Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic Means